500 years ago, a legend
in China's Wild West...
Said that a monk and
his three disciples...
Wouldnt travel from the Middle
Earth to the city of Shache...
To collect a bundle
of century-old sutras.
Legend has it, that only this
monk can translate those sutras.
Then, everyone would be so moved...
that they would forever
forswear killing,
and follow this monk to
the World f Ultimate Bliss,
where there is no war but eternal peace.
Master Tripitaka's come for the sutras!
Hurrah!
It's Master Tripitaka!
Great! They finally arrived in Shache.
Oh goodness, please dont.
Oh sugar! Song and dance,
thats Master's thing!
Wukong, what are you
doing staring at a pillar?
Someone once told me...
The best way to keep a secret
is to tell it to a hole.
Then seal it with mud.
I wanted to tell this hole my secret.
But before I opened my
mouth, a centipede bit me.
Tell it to a tree up in the mountains!
Not to a pillar!
You sure look depressed,
certainly not over the centipede.
Right! But I dont understand why.
Maybe there are demons?
Are you thick or what?
Wukong has
Burning-All-Seeing eyes.
He'd have seen any demon
when we entered town.
Makes sense. All the
guys and gals came out.
I didnt see anything fishy.
The pretty girls werent hiding,
Kids?
We didnt see any kids all morning.
Oh sugar!
Tripitaka, if we dont take
you to the free spirits...
to exchange for our kidnapped
childen before dawn...
they will feed them to
the Millenium Bug Demon.
I guess this isnt your lucky day!
Yeah!
What impudence!
Master!
How dare you set us up?
Wukong.
Remember how I told you
not to lose your temper?
Let me tame these folks by virtue, okay?
Pshaw! All your do is yak
about virtue and morality
And now you want to act cool?
Hey, show some respect!
Wuneng, I know...
You have prejudices, but I am confident.
Just watch me move them with my words
Citizens of Shache...
Sir, why should you bother?
Dont try to cut down
folks if your hands shake
See how this chopper dangles?
A sorry sight? Dont you say?
Attack my master? Take that!
Could you take better aim? Gosh!
If we eat Tripitaka's flesh,
we shall have eternal life.
And rule the world forever!
Allow me.
What... do... you... want...
Lets... settle... this... amicably?
Oh no!
Did I say something wrong?
Want to play with me?
You're not good enough.
Your hair doesnt work? Try some of mine
I almost forgot. I dont need
hair to summon my little monkeys.
I will, therefore I
am. Thats the royal way!
Transform!
Wukong!
Wukong! Are you okay? Wukong!
Master... take care of yourself
Piggy, you're a good boy
and I worry most about you...
You're stupid and your kung-fu sucks.
A kind heart is useless, you
will only get yourself killed.
How dare you look down
on me! I'll show you!
Piggy!
Come back!
Wukong!
Will you shut up?
Listen. This Sea-calming
Needle will take you to safety.
Im not leaving. I'll tame
these demons with virtue, huh?
Will you stop this huh
huh huh, its so annoying.
Huh?
Stop it!
What do you want?
Huh?
Since you like huh huh huh so much...
Keep on with it
Cotton candy? Do you
really think I'm that easy?
Not cotton candy. They are gold threads.
I'm going on a killing spree
today. Get out of my way.
Wukong, stop playing the bully
You cant fool me! Let me go!
If you want the golden
staff to obey you...
say I love you for 10,000 years.
To stop it, say I dont love you
Wukong, let me down!
Listen to your master, let me down!
Get out of here
Master!
What madness has been happening
in the past six months.
Its either raining
stones or strange eggs.
Now there is this idiot
He's no idiot. He's
Wukong, the love-sick king
How do you know?
Cant you see his golden staff?
But what fine skin and far
complexion for a monkey.
Thats him who wooed the
Purple Fairy 500 years ago?
Dont be silly
Eros? Thats a joke.
What do you know? Women
go crazy for guys like him
If only Heavens gave
me a second chance...
i'd tell this girl...
I love you!
If this romance must be
finite, let it last...
10,000 years
Shut up!
Since Wuking's here,
Tripitaka must be around too.
Fool Ping!
Here, coming
The name is Cool Ping.
What?
The name is Cool Ping, not Fool Ping.
You're not a fool? Your
daughter's a dead giveaway.
Get her daughter to guard him
That thing? Are you sure?
She's perfect
All the other girls drool at pretty boys
but her daughter will
never be turned on,
and he'll find her a total turn-off
Excuse me.
How did you wake up so soon?
Is it because of my beauty?
What? Are your trying to
charm me with a voice so sexy?
Huh?
I may be pretty, but I'm no pushover.
Hell that no fury like a beauty
scorned. Havent you heard?
Dont think I'll fall for
you because you're Eros
I'm frigid. No man has
ever captured my heart.
No, listen to me, Miss Meiyan.
How did you know my name?
I know I'm famous among imps...
but dont you plan on loving me...
because I'll end it as soon as you do.
Even if its for 100,000 years.
You dropped something
i think you dropped it
Shut up!
I didnt say anything
I just knew you'd say that
Your silence wont work on me
Evil does not lie down with good.
I'm evil through and through.
No goodness can touch me.
Can you let me go?
Of course not!
You might be so tempted by
my beauty that you'd attack me
I consider that a very
distant possibility
i saw through you and
you're shamed, right?
You look like an educated man,
and not totally unscrupulous.
Fine! I'll wager my virginity on that
These are gold threads, only
a womars saliva can melt them.
How dare you?
Taking advantage of me?!
I'm not afraid
Evil folks like us
dont prey on the weak.
And we meant what we said
What impudence!
How dare you imitate
my sexy mouth movements!
I'm sorry, I'm not as sexy as you...
Miss Meiyan.
Your name means beauty,
but I really cant see any.
You...
Sorry!
Goodness! I almost fell for it
No wonder they say all
good people are tricky
They're so right
No need to make me angry. I
have zero feelings for you.
If I get angry, that'd
mean I have feelings.
So I will not get angry. I may
even set you loose. Take that!
Yummie!
Im very thirsty. Can I
have some water please?
Yes of course
We are evil but not bad people.
Why should I mistreat you?
Thanks
What was that for?
For trying to seduce
me with good manners
You think I dont know?
Soon you'll be too weak and
force me to feed you the water.
And then when I hold
you up, you'll lean over
What am I going to do?
I cant push you away, and
I cannot push you away.
Just give me some water,
promise I'll drink it myself
Why should I trust you?
You win! You're such a talker
What must I do to get some water?
Dont ask!
If i dont, you'll give me water?
I said dont ask!
Even Buddha would go crazy
Not taking advantage of me?
What are you doing
with your lips so close?
You want to kiss me, bastard?!
I just want some water.
Will you give it to me?
Okay! You can kiss me once.
Then you're on your way.
Otherwise I'll kill you.
Oh sugar!
Now I understand why my
disciples find me annoying
Good for you You're not
without shame and you didnt...
I'm sorry. My mistake. Sorry!
Please stop talking, please
Since you admit your
fault, I forgive you.
Fine.
I'll get you some water,
but dont try to run away.
Or I'll break your legs
Who is it?
What an enormous egg!
I wonder who laid it
how can you be so ugly,
yet so beautiful inside?
Dont flatter me, you're disgusting.
Dont flirt with me!
I flirt with you?
What did you just say?
I said I wanted water
Are you playing tricks with me?
Why are you doing this to me?
Are you afraid now?
Watch out! Beware!
That means you know you're wrong
You dont know sorcery? Then say
'I love you for 10,000 years'
Son of a gun!
I beg you!
Well, what the heck...
I love you for 10,000 years
Stop, stop!
I dont love you
Stop, stop
It only works when you
say it holding the staff
Hurry up, say it.
You're so heartless,
I said I love you...
and I'll never change. Us evil people...
I know.
Dont say it to me, say it to the staff
That's more like it
I dont love you.
Stop fighting. I, Tripitaka, am here.
You're Tripitaka?
Get Tripitaka!
Whats going on?
Whose troops are these?
How dare they attack us?
Wake up. Dont die on me. Wake up!
Mom, dont die
i wont. I was faking it
Listen to your mom good
This Watershed Pearl
can carry two persons
Take Tripitaka to some
place where you can be alone,
Find an opportunity and eat him
Then you'll live forever
and enjoy eternal youth
When those bastards die,
no one will bully you.
I'm not afraid of those bullies.
But I know people make
fun of you because I'm ugly
Nonsense!
You're the prettiest thing on earth.
Remember, find a
chance and eat Tripitaka
I have to go.
Mom, I cant do it.
I've fallen in love with him
I never thought my
husband would be a monk
Take that!
I'm going
My Lord, we've lost Tripitaka
We have his disciples, surely
he'll come back for them.
Who made this Watershed Pearl?
A little poke and it fell to pieces
We'd have been fine if you
didnt stop to ask for directions
It's pitch dark here
Whats wrong with asking
a fish for directions?
Who knew it'd poke a hole in the
pearl pointing here and there?!
Thats not a fish, its a lobster
Why didnt you warn me?
You're evil and I'm
good; we cant communicate.
Hello, Lord Chancellor Tortoise
What happened to you?
This is all Wukong's fault.
He stole the Sea-calming Needle
and fouled up our ecosystem
Now the Dragon King throws up all
day, and we have to move ashore
Isnt that our Needle?
Yes... thats Wukong's Gold Staff
He is in trouble now, I hope
you can help me save him.
I can use some help myself
Give us back our Needle
Lord Chancellor, thats
not the proper procedure
What procedure?
This is now Wukong's Gold Staff
I should return it to him
first before you go ask him
With his consent, he'll return it to you
Thats proper procedure.
He stole our Needle, and
we have to seek his consent?
Stealing is theft...
Which is a legal issue, and
distinct from our situation here...
Damn your mother! Just
give me back our Needle!
My mother didnt steal your
Needle, she cant return it to you
Let him go!
Give me back our
Needle, or I'll kill you.
That again is improper procedure.
Improper again?
Of course
i dont have your Needle. She has it.
How can you take away
her Needle and kill me?
If you kill me, she will
never return it to you
But it doesnt mean she
will even if you spare me
So the issue of my life and
death is in her hands, not yours.
Right!
If I kill you, its because good
and evil dont make bedfellows.
You're a tortoise and I'm a
lizard, and we are both imps
If I dont do something, no one will
Then what are you waiting for?
All right.
Kill him...
Kill his mother!
Should I kill him or his mother?
Kill him, get a move on!
Kill his mother!
I have nothing against his
mother, why should I kill her?
Damn you. Are you going to do it or not?
I'm not killing his mother
Besides I dont know
her or where she lives
Thats right. My mother's hard to find.
Damn you!
Lord Chancellor Tortoise
Tripitaka, you killed
my Lord Chancellor?
No, I had nothing to do with it
Kill him!
I love you for 10,000 years
Now what?
We're on the run. Can
you show some emotions?
What have we done?
Why are we on the run?
With all those imps coming
at us, I had to fight them off
Exactly. Why did you
have to start a fight?
Dont you evil people
ever reason with anyone?
Must you always use violence?
Reason? You just reasoned
that tortoise to death.
I got nothing to do with his death!
You got everything to do with his death
Your last sentence was so loaded.
'My mother is hard to find'.
But my mother always moves
houses and is hard to find!
Now we must turn to the Heavens for help
You turning yourself in?
I'm an upstanding guy and
I know right from wrong
I'm not like you. I
have nothing to fear.
Great! Tough guy! I'll go with you
You shut your mouth when we get
there. Let me do the talking.
We're going to Heavens
But I dont know the way.
Can you please take us?
Will you get a grip on yourself?
We're dead meat!
Heavens South Gate
Lets go over there
No, dont! Come back here!
Hello? Anyone home?
How did you get inside?
Come back out here now, hurry!
Oh, I'm inside?
Come out.
This is fun
What a gigantic ink stone
Tripitaka, you have
some nerve coming here
Be quiet!
I told you to hold your tongue
The four Heavenly Knights.
Wukong is in trouble. I
come to beg for your help
And if I dont, are you
going to kill me too?
You know I never killed
anything or anyone
How do you explain the
blood on your clothes?
Thats Lord Chancellor Tortoise's.
So it wasnt a false accusation
I have nothing to do with his death
How did he die?
I talked him to death
I mean...
See? You keep saying it,
now I start believing it.
Believing what?
You said you're innocent,
that you had nothing to fear.
Right, I'm not afraid...
Want to fight? Get him!
I love your for 10,000 years
How dare you?! Kill that succubus!
Heavenly Knight Cengzhang is dead!
Stop looking. Lets scram
We're off again?
Tripitaka, you murderer...
Sorry to stain you with blood
Lets break up
I'm good and you're evil,
lets go our separate ways.
Break up? You really are heartless!
I saved your life and
you're throwing me out?
You should talk!
You beat up people for no reason,
and now you killed a Heavenly Knight
Are you blaming me? You provoked it!
I provoked it?
I didnt say a word when
you men were talking
I gave you all the respect you wanted
Its how you said why should I
be afraid? You're so arrogant.
It'd have pissed off anyone.
You tripped him, and
that got people going
I tripped him because...
Leave!
Dont you love me anymore?
I never loved you.
I dont believe you
Read my lips
I dont love you
Say it again
I dont love you. Get lost!
Scram.
C'mon, lets not be mad with
each other. Please love me.
I'm a monk
I dont know anything
about falling in love.
My love is for all mortals
Why, that should include me
Except you!
You really hate me that much?
Yes.
You dont care about me at all?
No!
Then stay being a monk
Three little words
I love you. Say it!
No.
Have you ever seen a monk fall in love?
Or a monk having a girl
friend? I wont say it.
Say it!
No, not even if you kill me!
Okay, I understand.
Nuts! Forcing people to say...
I'll wait a little longer.
You will come looking for me
I think I've waited long enough
Oh sugar! He really
went looking for me...
but in the wrong direction
If he comes back and doesnt see me...
he'll be heart-broken
What will the poor thing do without me?
Better surprise him
with a nice veggie dinner
I'll cook a nice dinner no matter what!
Its do or die!
I'm starving, I need to eat something.
I love you for 10,000 years
What is it? I'm vegetarian.
I'll take it up with Wukong
Let us, the Five Great
Sects kill this bitch!
The Five Great Sects?
We're going to eat you.
Can you at least react?
I'm not afraid.
This bitch's fallen out of love
Got dumped and dont
care to live, right?!
Fine! Let me make it easy for you.
Stop! Spare her!
You scum are worse than evil
Eat me, I'm Tripi...
Stop it!
Get lost. I dont want to see you.
Gentlemen, I'm Tripitaka.
You're so stupid! You're
asking to be their dinner
So this is Tripitaka...
You're sacrificing yourself
for this ugly bitch?
Let her go, darling!
So both master and
disciple are ladies'men.
I dont believe you're that great.
Unless you crawl between
Crimson Kid's legs.
Yeah...
Crawl and I'll break up with you again!
C'mon!
Crimson Kid never changes his underwear
Hats off to you if you
can survive that stench
C'mon, over here
See how Tripitaka treats his woman
Tripitaka, you're my main man
Yo held your breath and got it over with
I see all of you have a heart of gold.
In the future you must love
each other and love thy enemies
What do we do if the enemies attack us?
Just dont retaliate
but move them with your love
What if they want to kill you?
Never fight back.
But make them lay down
their weapons with your love
Tripitaka
- you got some nerve killing a Heavenly Knight.
No he didnt. I killed him.
Thats enough!
Stop protecting me.
Darling, look at this loving couple
Tripitaka, I'm behind you on this one.
Right! Exactly! All the way!
Impudent demons
Help him and I beat you senseless
What are you staring at? Dont try me.
I wont fight you; I'll
move you with love.
I love you
Here I come!
Easy!
C'mon!
Who's next?
Take it easy.
We have a power stronger
than their swords: Our Life!
Right, Tripitaka?!
I was only kidding.
We have here hundreds of thousands...
I love you for 10,000 years
Calm down!
Watch out!
Oh sugar!
Out of my way!
I have killed...
I cant be a charitable monk anymore...
Please give him some space
You two who feigned death,
and the Heavenly Knight,
Get out of my sight!!
Dont let Tripitaka know.
Thats one nasty trick!
She's a real bitch
Get your chopsticks ready
for some Tripitaka-stew
Quit blaming yourself
I know you killed because of me
I know that I'm your
liablitiy. I'd be going.
If you still want to save
Wukong, talk to the imps.
They're a decent lot
I'm leaving
Do you miss me already?
I always thought that Heavens
are kind and charitable.
But what I saw today was...
Moral chaos and indiscriminate
killing of the innocent.
Previously we stand on the
two poles of good and evil
but now I've become a murdering monster,
an equal among evil-doers
Right!
From now on we'll work together...
get the Imps to save Wukong...
get him to join us and
enjoy arson and murder.
Yes.
Let us strike palms and
set off to rescue Wukong
What is it?
I'll go with you to rescue Wukong,
but remember, if you leave me again...
I wont give you another chance.
Deal.
Though I lied to him,
its for his own good
I told the imps that
Tripitaka had been poisened,
and is only fit for
consumption after a month.
I'm praying to keep the
truth from them long enough...
for them to help
Tripitaka rescue Wukong.
Its hard to be human,
but harder to be an imp.
You must cultivate a demonic attitude,
so that even at first glance, folks
will marvel: What demonic charm!
Alright!
Kid, you know how to bully people?
You know how to bully people?
Fighting back? Good. Take that!
Stop moving. I'm applying
this ointment on you.
On me where?
This is killing me.
Women of this sort have no shame.
Twisting and twirling
with a stranger in public.
I'd never do that
I'd only do hot-dancing...
with the man I love
under a star-lit sky...
in the silence of the night.
Meiyan, yesterday Green Snake
taught me a really cool dance.
I'll teach you.
Not interested.
Did I say something wrong?
She hasnt spoken all morning.
Take this!
Thats one knockout punch on my face,
Yet I also deeply felt
his wild masculinity.
So every night when
my lion is sleeping...
I'd sit by him like a lamb...
and admire him in silence. Take that.
I've chained you two together.
The bout will only stop when one
of you begs for mercy. Understand?
Ready, go!
Spit...
What?
I love you for 10,000 years.
Help me carry the buckets.
Damn you! Thats cheating.
I won.
Yeah, by spitting.
Time to get my man a toupee
and send him into the world.
I convinced them to rescue Wukong.
You're so cute.
Why she's looking better and better.
Dont come back until you've
divorced your ugly wife.
Have you seen Meiyan?
She went to gather firewood.
It may snow later on.
Get in, quick!
Lean against me if you're cold.
I told Tripitaka that I was
teaching him Silkworm magic.
Now he comes to this
forest every night...
dressed like Mr. Football!
Spin a web...
I spin a web...
another web.
I spin a web hard.
Spin a web
Here...
No? More like spitting
than spinning a web.
But for Wukong, I must
keep on practicing.
Its you!
Its me.
This is a hold up!
I thought we were
friends, how could you?
Well, you just robbed
me. Give me back my knife.
Sorry.
Once a demon, always a demon.
You're demon I'm human.
We left the Earth before the Ice Age.
So I am your ancestor.
My flying saucer had an
accident inside the time tunnel,
and it fell down here.
What rubbish!
You're my ancestor? Do
I look like an idiot?
Whats the big deal? We've
been back a few times...
even to Egypt...
and left behind some
triangular transmitter.
Its been more than a month,
he should be cleansed.
Eat him and we'll have eternal youth.
Great, a big feast.
Meiyan, you have a visitor.
Mom, how did you find me?
Father Soil told me. Have
you eaten Tripitaka yet?
Well? Tell me
You let him off?
I know it. You've fallen for him.
But why?
Because he calls me by my name
Pshaw! But why a stupid monk?
Hes given it up
Does he love you?
Hes become an imp
Goodness, some daughter you are!
You converted Tripitaka!
Thats some achievement!
We used to live here too
But because of war, we
went to another planet...
to find a land of peace.
I thought things would
improve after we left,
but you're still fighting.
If its so wonderful, why
did you run away from home?
Of course I have my reasons
I dont like the guy my
father wanted me to marry.
I want to find my own.
Have you found him yet?
Yes. I was sitting inside the cocoon...
and he poked his head in to look at me.
His soulful eyes captivated
me. Its a bit like yours.
You're not talking about me, are you?
I have no feeling for you whatsoever.
I've heard that before
If you dont believe me, kiss me and see
I knew you'd say that
Or I can kiss you and see
A monk chatting up chicks?
You ugly slut, you have no shame!
Who is ugly? Look at the mirror!
Cut the crap! Kill her!
Whats going on?
Mom!
What is it?
She wants to take Tripitaka away!
Kill her!
Yeah, kill her
What evil demons are these?
Mom.
Look
Want to play games?
Try my Multiple Transformation Magic!
I'm real and unreal, unreal and real
That'll teach you!
Fire!
Damn! I said Multiple
Transformation Magic...
Why is everyone hitting me?
Too much!
Invincible Wheels Of Fire!
We had nothing to do with it
Really, we had nothing to do with it
Its all that dog's fault,
right from the beginning
She said we should eat Tripitaka!
What?
Honest! That other day...
It was her idea to play
Heavenly Guards to kill imps.
No, no.
Listen to me
What do you mean no?
She also taught us
how to rescue Wukong...
Its all a ploy to kill Master!
Right, I can vouch for that
I can vouch for that
I can vouch for that too.
No, I was lying to them
I'm here. Let them go
Yes, your Highness
You cant go there alone,
I'll come with you. Let go!
No! I wont.
Let go!
Whats wrong with being ugly?
But why lie to me?
Why?
Mom...
I'm not your Mom. My
daughter died at birth.
I found you at the riverbank
and brought you home.
People laughed at me
and called me a fool.
I got to go
No!
I may be ugly, but please dont leave me.
This was next to you when I found you
I'm not garbage. Dont
just throw me away.
I'm not just a thing. I have a name!
My name is Meiyan.
I have a name!
We'll soon reach Shache.
Lets go and rescue Wukong.
IS THERE NOT A WAY IN THIS MORTAL WORLD
TO EMBRACE BOTH MY FAITH AND MY BELOVED?
I love you for 10,000 years, I love...
BORED OF FIGHTING
- DAY OFF
This is no time to go on strike
General Ba.
The tracks are too narrow and dark,
we cant carry out the bombing mission.
High-speed flying is too dangerous,
but if he slows down, the
Tree Spirit will get him.
Watch out!
No, we must get out of here!
Your Highness,
Morale is low. No one wants
to fight the monk's battle
Hes got his sutras anyway
Your Highness, we can hook up
with the time tunnel any time now.
I advice that we dont
miss this opportunity.
I'm not fighting this battle for
Tripitaka, but for the human race.
Our ancestors thought
leaving was a solution
And what happened?
Nothing's changed
All hopes and cultures are at stake
Run!
What was that?
Your Highness, a signal
from the time tunnel.
I love you for 10,000 years
Where are you?
I love you for 10,000 years, I love...
I didnt mean you!
Wheres your Gold Staff?
I love you for 10,000 years
Over here!
Lets rescue Wukong
Who's that?
Sir, a friendly warrior is
charging into underground
Give her the Doomsday Bomb.
Your master Tripitaka sent me.
But you're inside the
Tree Spirit's mouth.
How can you help us?
I love you for 10,000 years.
Are you coming or not?
I'm used to it here & i
have unfinished business
You know there is no
turning back, dont you?
I didnt know you were our princess
Please pardon my inospitality
Thats alright.
I'm very happy to know you.
Have you found him yet?
Yes. I was sitting inside the cocoon...
the soulful eyes captivated me.
I promised you to rescue Wukong,
but I also said, I wouldnt
give you another chance
Wukong, when we get to
the Celestial Court...
I'll tell the Jade Emperor...
That you had nothing to do with
the death of the Heavenly Knight.
I'll take full responsibility for it.
Then why are we...
They were our sin from previous
lives, soon to be swept away by wind.
Lets go!
I've come to beg forgiveness
Why would you say so?
We know you're not responsible for
the death of the Heavenly Knight.
What?
I've come to turn myself in.
I killed Lord Chancellor
Tortoise and the Heavenly Knight.
Tripitaka has nothing to do with them
You have committed most serious crimes
though you are not one of us, we
dont tolerate violation of our laws.
You're sentenced to death and
shall be summarily executed.
Do you have any final words?
I once experienced true love.
But I didnt treasure it.
I only regret after losing it.
The pains of life on earth...
Thats enough!
Stop parroting shopworn chliches!
But do you know why I
recite them every day?
...because I feel guilty.
Like how you chant the Heart Sutra
every time you make a mistake.
Sir, the Emperor has ordered
the execution of the prisoner.
Wukong.
No. You've travelled so far
on the path to enlightenment.
Dont make another mistake.
Let me reason with the Emperor.
Reason about what?
Someone's taken the fall.
Turn a blind eye to it
What is there to talk or reason?
Tramps like her perish
by the dozen every hour.
Good!
You rulers of the universe,
do you know what love is?
500 years ago, Wukong wrecked
havoc in the Celestial Court.
Today, its my turn!
Wish I was that cool back then.
Tripitaka assaulted an official!
Meiyan, I've come to rescue you.
Destroy the Gold Staff!
NO!
Tripitaka!
Repent or you will regret it.
Let go of him.
Impudence!
Want me to slit your throat?
No, please calm down.
Whats an old fart doing in a skirt?
Let go of him, now!
Yeah, its a butchers knife alright.
Imbeciles! Ignoramus!
Is it a sin to love someone?
Its a crime for her to love Tripitaka
and kill a knight in self-defense
but would a knight be put
on trial if he'd killed her?
Would he be held accountable?
Is it a sin to love someone?
No.
Of course you'd say
that, you're married.
Tripitaka.
Be a man, get up!
I know.
Buddha.
Wukong offended his superiors
out of love for his Master.
That I can understand.
But why'd you think, harming the
Emperor could help the situation?
How'd it differ from
them do harm to Tripitaka?
Buddha, please pardon Master.
I shall accept all consequences.
Jade Emperor, let me handle this.
Its all yours
Tripitaka, why do you
wish to save this woman?
Shes done so much for me...
If you do save her, what then?
I'll stay with her.
Is that what you want?
If I were to tell you...
that you only have until
sundown to stay with her
How would you feel?
I'm willing
Ah, then your love is limited.
Have you ever thought that
love may not bring any results?
The pursuit of result
is a limiting activity.
I believe this woman is
prepared to sacrifice herself
and never thought about the
chances of staying with you.
Only a love that asks for no
returns is truly everlasting.
I'm back.
Tripitaka is not free of desires
and not ready for deification.
He needs to start all over
again. Do you understand?
You have violated Heavenly Laws.
I can spare you a death sentence,
but not a living penalty.
Do you accept the punishment?
Buddha said, we needed to
overcome another 81 tasks.
Wukong is waiting for us
at the Five-Finger Mountain
Lets go find him.
THE GREATEST DISTANCE DIVIDES US
NOT BECAUSE YOU ARE OBLIVIOUS TO MY LOVE
WHEN I STAND IN FRONT OF YOU
BUT BECAUSE WE LOVE EACH OTHER
KNOWING FATE WILL FOREVER KEEP US APART
No, I wont ride you.
Not in this life or any other.
What is it?
Whats the matter with you?
Get up, will you?
Get up!
How can I ride you if you dont get up?
You've become so impossible.
Meiyan...
I'm only kidding.
OCR subtitle authoring by jmungus